secuwa.org 2014-04-30

# Privacy Policy & Security | School Employees Credit Union of Washington | Seattle - Spokane

**Download printable version of Privacy Policy** **.**

[ **View our informational videos on a variety of security topics.**](http://www.secuwa.org/mstinc/grp/security_page/)

 **Our goal is to protect School Employees Credit Union** **and its membership**. **We recommend you always double-check your account activity through Online Banking** for any unusual transactions and notify us immediately of any suspicious activity. If you have any questions, please contact us at 206-628-4010 or 1-888-628-4010.

 **PLEASE NOTE:** No employee of School Employees Credit Union of Washington will ever call you and ask for any credit union account numbers or associated passwords (PINs). Should you receive such a call, **do not** divulge any information and contact us immediately.

 **Help foil identity theft!** You can now add a personalized security "question and answer password" to block other people from accessing your credit union accounts. (The security question would be used for phone and in-person transactions. Your electronic and online transactions already are password-protected.) To set up your password, please call 1-888-628-4010 weekdays from 7:30 a.m. to 5:30 p.m. **It takes just minutes!**

## PRIVACY POLICY

School Employees Credit Union of Washington values the trust you place in us as one of your financial service providers.

We want to let you know about our privacy policies and practices. We believe that maintaining the confidentiality and security of our members' and former members' nonpublic personal information ("personal information") is a fundamental responsibility.

While information is important to providing quality service, we are committed to protecting your personal information.

## Personal Information We Collect

We may collect personal information about members and former members from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications, online registrations, or other forms, such as your name, address, Social Security number, assets, and income;
  * Information about your transactions with us and others, such as your account balance, payment history, and credit card usage; and
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as your credit history and credit worthiness.

## How We Use Your Personal Information

We do not sell personal information about our members, former members, or their accounts, to others. We may disclose the personal information we collect, as described above, to other service providers in order to service or process your transactions with us or to inform you of additional products or services we believe may be of interest to you. These service providers may include financial service providers (such as companies that provide settlement, billing, processing, and other services) as well as other service providers (such as technology processing companies).

We may also disclose personal information, as described above, to other third parties as permitted or required by law in order, for example, to protect against fraud, to protect the confidentiality or security of our business records, or to comply with applicable legal requirements.

We may also disclose personal information we collect, as described above, to third parties that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have a joint marketing agreement. When we establish such relationships, we require that the other parties limit their use of that information, and we prohibit them from sharing or using it for any purposes other than those for which the information is provided.

## Protection and Security of Your Personal Information

We limit access to personal information to those with a legitimate business reason for such access. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information from being accessed by unauthorized persons

## Accuracy of Your Information

If for any reason you feel our records contain inaccurate personal information, please notify us at 1-888-628-4010.

We will promptly update or correct our records.

### Thank You for Your Trust 

We value our relationship with our members and appreciate the opportunity to serve your financial needs. We are committed to protecting your personal information.

## Internet Security Statement

### Information Collected

We do not collect information that personally identifies a user of our web site unless the user voluntarily provides that information to us. When you access our web site, we automatically collect information that cannot personally identify you, including the date and time of access, the domain you use, the web site you last visited before accessing our site, and the route you travel while visiting within our web site. This information is used to measure the number of visitors to our web site and to provide better service to users through improved web site design and navigation.

We do not market our products and services to children, and we will not knowingly collect or maintain information from children via the Internet.

### Member Only Areas (Online Banking) (E-statements)

Personal identification information (for example, account number, personal identification number (PIN), and password) is collected when a valid credit union member with active account(s) has registered to enter the secure online transactions area of our web site. This personal identification information enables us to regulate access to those who request such access and can provide the correct personal information. To protect yourself, it is important that you keep your personal identification information confidential. Select PINs and passwords that are unique to you and not easily guessed, and if possible, change them periodically. Take care to see that others are not able to view the information you enter when you use a protected area of a web site.

### Cookies

We use "cookies," which are temporary text files a web site stores on a visitor's web browser to carry forward information the visitor enters on one page to others he or she visits. The cookies help to protect the privacy of a member's [customer's] transaction privacy by automatically terminating online sessions when he or she forgets to log out. When used, cookies cannot capture a user's email address, obtain data from the user's hard drive, or gain confidential or sensitive information about the user. A cookie also cannot be read by any web site other than the one that sent the cookie.

### Online Forms

We provide online forms and applications to better serve the needs of our members. Personal information provided via an online form is used to process the member's request for service. Our online forms are sent directly via our secure internal network. (See E-mail, below.)

### E-mail

In general, Internet e-mail messages are not secure, unless they are encrypted. You should use discretion before submitting any personal or financial information via e-mail. Information communicated via e-mail messages traveling through the Internet may be intercepted, collected, used or disclosed by others. If you are concerned about the security of email communications, please send your forms or correspondence through the postal service or use the telephone to contact us directly.

### Links to Other Sites

Our web site contains links to other web sites. These sites are not under our control. They may collect information about you that we do not. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of linked web sites.
